<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.5//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.5/docbookx.dtd" [
<!ENTITY % BOOK_ENTITIES SYSTEM "RestComm_User_Guide.ent">
%BOOK_ENTITIES;
]>
<!-- chapter id nickname: ittsss -->
<chapter id="Why_RestComm">
	<title>Why Use &SHORT_PLATFORM_NAME;</title>
	<para>There are many reasons to use &SHORT_PLATFORM_NAME; and below are a few</para>
	<para>
 		
	</para>
	
	
<para>
What you can build with &SHORT_PLATFORM_NAME; is often limited by your imagination. Because of the flexibility that is built into the system, you will be able to create, with little effort, commercial grade applications like the following: 



<itemizedlist mark='opencircle'>

<listitem>
<para>
An application that will call hundreds of clients and play a pre-recorded marketing message (electoral campaign, products marketing, etc.)
</para>
</listitem>

<listitem>
<para>
An application that will automatically call people and warn them of an impending emergency like hurricane, flooding, etc.
</para>
</listitem>
<listitem >
<para>
An application to reserve a table at your favorite restaurant or order meals like Pizzas.
</para>
</listitem>
<listitem>
<para>
An application to perform telephone surveys interacting with users automatically
</para>
</listitem>
<listitem>
<para>
Applications to schedule/reschedule, cancel and delay doctors appointment. 
</para>
</listitem>
<listitem>
<para>
Applications to offer users at the airport, upgrades from economy to business class or alert passengers to special offers
</para>
</listitem>

<listitem>
<para>
Applications to offer businesses a tool to alert customers to current discounts and special offers. 
</para>
</listitem>

<listitem>
<para>
An application that will interact with major brands (Cisco, Avaya,etc) SIP endpoints. This is great because you are not 
tied to closed source platform. &SHORT_PLATFORM_NAME; lets you access the source code and adapt your application to talk
to anyone using SIP protocol. 
</para>
</listitem>

<listitem>
<para>
 &SHORT_PLATFORM_NAME; can also be used to setup a short code SMS business that will allow small and large business to get clients to subscribe and receive
 marketing or special deals.
</para>
</listitem>

</itemizedlist>

</para>>
<para>
These are just a few selections of what you can achieve with &SHORT_PLATFORM_NAME;. The next section will explain how you can create simple applications with little effort. 
</para>
	
	
	
</chapter>
